Hello friends, if you have also taken
any policy in ICICI Prudential Life Insurance
and you want to manage it online, then for this
you will have to
login to your policy account.  In today's
video, I am going to tell you
how to login to ICICI Prudential Life Insurance policy and
how to manage the policy after logging in.
So let's start the video without any delay.
[Music]
Open any web browser.  Like
I have opened Google Chrome browser
and type www.icc
prolif.com
and press enter.  After this, the official page
of ICICI Primary Life Insurance will
open in front of you.
You will see the login option on the top right side.
Click on it.  In this you will see an option
Individual.  Click on it.
After this, the
login window will open in front of you like this.  If you have
already registered in it, then you
can login to the policy account by entering the registered mobile number or email ID and entering the password in it.  And if you have
come here for the first time then first you will have to register in it.
Here you will see an option of New User.
Click on it.
After this, a page like this will open in front of you.
You
can either enter the email ID registered in the policy or
enter the mobile number or
enter the policy number.  Like I
entered the policy number in it [music].
After this, enter the date of birth in it.  Like
on your policy bond.  After this you have to
submit it.  Now we will generate OTP.
OTP will be sent to your registered mobile number
and email ID.  As
you can read here.  And OTP will be
sent to your registered email ID and
mobile number.  Click on Send OTP.
OTP has been sent to your mobile number and email ID.  Like you can read.
OTP is sent to your registered
email ID and mobile number.  We will make it ok.
Enter that OTP code in it and
create a new password here.  Password
length: Password should be 8 to 16 characters
and there should not be any special character other than @#g in the password.
Let
me put the password in it.  To confirm,
enter the password again
and then submit it.
The password will be set upon submission.  As you
can see your password has been updated
successfully.  After OKing this, you will
login to the policy.  The
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance page will
open again in front of you.  Click on login again.
After this the individual will
click on it.  The login window will open in front of you.
In this we will enter the registered mobile number or
email ID and enter the password that we have just
created
and from here we will
select dashboard and sign in.  After this you will be
logged into the policy account.  Here at the top
you will see the name of the policy holder.
Here you will see your policy.
Here the policy name, policy number,
next, due date and premium amount are
given.  If you have more than one policy in it,
then you
can link the second policy by going to My Policy.  And
your current policy will be visible here.  You
can check the policy details by clicking on it.
In this you will get all the details of the policy.
After this you
can check the profile by clicking here.  In this
way your personal details will be shown here.
Such as the date of birth of the policy holder
, his name, gender, marital status,
PAN number etc.  Contact details are given below this.
After this you
can check the transaction details by clicking here.
In this you will see many service options.
You can use these options as per your need.
After this
you can download and check the statements from here.
Here you will see all types of policy
statements.  You
can download all these statements from here.  So
friends, in this way you can manage the
policy by logging in to ICICI Prudential Life Insurance.  That's all
in this video.
If you liked the video then please
like and share it and if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel then please
subscribe and also
click on the bell icon so that you can get the
notification of every new video of ours
first.  Thanks for watching this
video.